Guide to the William Nicoson papers, 1954-2007
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections & Archives
- Series 5: Newsclipping, 1960-1985; (2 boxes)
  - The Connection-April 6, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    325.25
  - The Connection-January 26, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    325.24
  - The Connection-December 14, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    325.28
  - The Connection-June 8, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    325.27
  - The Connection-April 6, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    325.26
  - The Times-November 1, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    325.37
  - The Connection-August 1, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    325.34
  - The Connection-September 26, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    325.35
  - The Times-September 27, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    325.36
  - Fairfax Board Gives Reston Center a Place in History-February 14, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    325.31
  - The Most Influential People In This Country Reston-January 5, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    325.30
  - The Washington Post-June 17, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    325.33
  - The Connection, Volume IV, Number 51-December 19, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    325.38
  - The Connection, Volume V, Number 12-January 9, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    325.39
  - The Connection-May 29, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    325.47
  - The Reston Times-May 16, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    325.46
  - Reston Celebrating It's 20th Year!-May 16, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    325.45
- Series 6: General Information, 1954-1999; (6 boxes)
  The information in this series covers a variety of topics such as Town and Country Planning Association and New Communities Development. Also included are advertisements, slides and maps.
  - Market Survey of Wood Across Shopping Center-February, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    646.09
  - Biography-Jennie Lea Knight, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    323.09
  - Central Lancashire Development Corporation Agreement with Seniors, 1960s (Box 14, Folder 34)
    338.06
  - Proposed Bond Resolution, 1960s (Box 14, Folder 37)
    646.03
  - Traffic and Revenues Proposed Richmond Expressway System, 1960s (Box 14, Folder 38)
    646.04
  - Information on Campfire Girls, Household Services and Firewood, 1960s (Box 14, Folder 39)
    323.10
  - "Misues of the Misues Doctrine in Infringment Suit" by Nicoson, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    419.1
  - Policy Manual of Zoning Procedures, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    486.02
  - The Minutes Book of the Reston Music Center, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Expressway Routes Disclosed, Richmond Times Dispatch-October 23, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    646.11
  - Richmond Metropolitan Authority-Map, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    646.10
  - Richmond Expressway System, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    646.05
  - Arguments for New Towns, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    327.02
  - Fort Lincoln Prospectus, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - New Towns Research Seminar-Series I, Meetings 1-30-September 22, 29 and October 13, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    327.01
  - Achieving Racially and Economically Diversified New Communities, Duncah-November 17, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    328.05
  - Aspen Conference, 1970s (Box 15, Folder 7)
    326.26
  - Val D'Yerres, 1970s (Box 15, Folder 8)
    326.25
  - Standard Conveyance, 1970s (Box 15, Folder 9)
    326.24
  - Slides-General Subject Matter of The Columbia Process Workshop, 1970s (Box 15, Folder 10)
    326.07
  - Duplicates from The Columbia Process Workshop, 1970s (Box 15, Folder 11)
    326.08
  - Instruments of Housing Policy, 1970s (Box 15, Folder 12)
    326.19
  - Notes by R.W. Phelps, M.A., General Manager of the Central Lancashire New Town for the Egyptian Authorities on the Objectives and Methods of New Town Development in the United Kingdom, 1970s (Box 15, Folder 13)
    326.06
  - Bulletin Re/Max Regal Properties Incorporated, 1970s (Box 15, Folder 14)
    322.45
  - Richmond Metropolitan Authority, 1970s (Box 15, Folder 15)
    646.06
  - Stadsbyggnadsbyran AB, 1970s (Box 15, Folder 16)
    341.15
  - Where Have the Farmlands Gone?, 1970s (Box 15, Folder 17)
    341.01
  - Town and Country Planning Association "White Paper", "Land, The Inner Cities" and "The Redevelopment of the London Docklands", 1970s (Box 15, Folder 18)
    338.07
  - Heron House, 1970s (Box 15, Folder 19)
    323.19
  - Speech Outlines, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    334.18
  - Agenda for the Public Systems Planning Meeting-May 4, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    329.20
  - Progressive Methods of Building Design and Construction, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    329.03
  - The Washington Center for Metropolitan Studies: Managing Services for New Communities by Royce Hanson-October 25-28 (2 copies), 1970 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    330.32
  - Riverton New Community-July 8, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    330.12
  - Riverton: Housing Review of Preapplication Proposal-July 8, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    330.13
  - Preliminary Review of Riverton Planning-July 9, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    330.14
  - Staff Review Riverton Preapplication-July 10, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    330.16
  - Riverton Pre-Application Proposal-June 18, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    330.05
  - Columbia Conference, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    332.04
  - New Communities for the Tri-State Region/Tri-State Transportation Commission Volume II Proceedings of the new Communities Conference-May 10, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    333.09
  - Environmental Statement on the Proposed Riverton New Community Monroe County, New York-June 16, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    333.10
  - Report of U.S. Interagency Vaudreull Project Group-February, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    333.07
  - Report of U.S. Interagnecy Vaudreull Project Group-February, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    333.06
  - Housing Allowances: The Impact on Minority Families-December 21, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    334.10
  - AIA Journal, A National Proving Ground Minnesota Experimental Copy, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    334.02
  - Basic Documents, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    332.11
  - New School Course, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    332.05a
  - New School Course, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    332.05b
  - Financing Negatives, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    335.01
  - Information Material, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    335.04
  - Information Material, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    335.05
  - Flower Mound New Town: New Community Debentures, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    331.1
  - Down Towns-Town Centers Conference-Cincinnati, Ohio, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    419.7
    - Press Release: U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development, June 29, 1971; 1.
  - The American Institute of Architects-New Communities Conference, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    419.6
    - Presentation: William J. Nicoson, "In Search of the Public Interests in Land Use Controls", November 3-6, 1971; 1.
  - The Urban Life Center Conference on Education In New Communities, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    419.4
    - Bibliography: The American City Corporation Conference on Education in New Communities, February 24-26, 1971; 1.
    - Book chapter: George M. Robb; from "Workshop on Education held in Minneapolis" in Volume I: A Compendium of Publications Relating to Socio-Cultural Aspects, April 24-26, 1968; 2.
    - Book chapter: Sub-Committee of the Central Housing Advisory Committee from The Needs of New Communities: A Report on Social Provision in New and Expanding Communities (Chapter 4, "Education"), 1967; 3.
    - Article: Ellen Hoffman, The Progressive, "Old Towns for New Cities", September 1970; 4.
    - Morton Hoppenfeld, American Institute of Planners Journal, "A Sketch of the Planning-Building Process for Columbia, Maryland.", September 1970; 5.
    - Newsletter: American City Corporation, "Urban Life in New and Renewing Communities", January 1971; 6.
  - New Towns and Planned Communities, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    419.5
  - New Community Development: Planning Process Implementation and Emerging Social Concerns, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    333.4
  - The Council on Environmental Quality's 102 Monitor Report by John D. Pingell (Representative from Michigan)-March 1, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    335.14
  - Urban Land: News and Trends in Land Development, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    335.09
  - New Communities Development Handbook-May 20, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    336.01
  - New Communities Development Handbook-May 20, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    336.02
  - New Communities Development Handbook-May 20, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    336.03
  - Summary of New Communities Guaranteed by Housing and Urban Development (HUD), 1972 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    336.08
  - Urban Renewal-New Communities, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    335.03
  - Hand Book, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    420.3
  - Urban Land, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    486.04
  - Lawyers Title News, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    486.03
  - Richmond Metropolitan Authority, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    646.01
  - Richmond Metropolitan Authority Official Statement Dated October 3, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    646.13
  - Richmond Metropolitan Authority Expressway Revenue REfunding Bonds Series, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    646.12
  - 20th Century Fund, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    337.05
  - New Community Institute, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    336.07
  - Accounting, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    336.10
  - The Bureaucrat, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    486.01
  - Handbook Contract, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    419.8
    - Letter to the Editor: William J. Nicoson to Al Louis Ripskis, editor of Impact, 1973; 1.
  - Community Structure for National Growth, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    420.4
    - Report: William Nicoson, "Community Structure for National Growth", January 1973; 1.
  - Center for Urban and Regional Studies: The University of North Carolina-Chapel Hill, Evergreen House, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    338.01
  - City of Richmond Office of the City Manager, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    646.02
  - Richmond Expressway Progress Report Number 1-July 1, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    646.07
  - Commonwealth of Virginia, Department of Highways, Organization Guide-January, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    646.14
  - Annual Report: Traffic and Revenues, Richmond Metropolitan Authority, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    646.08
  - Redevelopment and Authority Chairman's Notes-July, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    323.02
  - The Planning Bookshop: Town and Country Planning Association, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    326.23
  - Town and Country Planning: Development Corporation Skills in Urban-February, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    341.07
  - Central Lancashire Development Corporation-May 2, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    341.08
  - Standard Building Licence, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    341.05
  - Bibliographic Printout on Building, 1980s (Box 20, Folder 9)
    326.10
  - The Bureaucrat, Volume 2, Number 1, 1980s (Box 20, Folder 10)
    326.01
  - Saint Anne's Episcopal Church Architectural Plans-April 18, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    325.32
  - "Planned Communities: Are They Worth It?", 1999 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Dissertation-"Suburbs of Tomorrow: 1960s New Towns and Transformation of the American Dream" I, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Dissertation-"Suburbs of Tomorrow: 1960s New Towns and Transformation of the American Dream" II, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Dissertation-"Suburbs of Tomorrow: 1960s New Towns and Transformation of the American Dream" III, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Series 7: Newspaper Columns, 1982-2007; (5 boxes)
  This series consists of paper and digital files containing original drafts and research materials for newspaper columns written by William Nicoson that were originally published in the Reston Connection during the late 1990s and early 2000s.
  - Reston Community Center, 2002-2005
    Includes the following articles: Your preference for RCC governors (not in MARS), Revolution at RCC, Polling for RCC governors, Business seats on RCC's board.
    - Reston Community Center
  - ABC's of Reston politics, April 9-19, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - ABC's of Reston politics, April 19, 1999
  - Amenities behind the employee surge: Who pays?, February 1999 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    Scope and Content
    Also includes: Storm clouds gather over RA (Reston Association), Rain storms over Reston Bring Financial Storms.
    - Amenities behind the employee surge: Who pays?, February 18, 1999
    - Rain storms over Reston Bring Financial Storms, February 15, 1999
    - Storm clouds gather over RA (Reston Association), February 8, 1999
  - An electoral silver lining? No, two, November 6-9, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - An electoral silver lining? No, two, November 9, 1999
  - Another Nixon is precedential (Walter Nixon), January 8-10, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Another Nixon is Precedential, January 10, 1999
  - Army of artists to occupy town center (GRACE festival), May 1999 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Army of artists to occupy town center (GRACE festival), May 6, 1999
  - The assessment cap forecasts a dismal future, January-March 2004 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - The assessment cap forecasts a dismal future, March 3, 2004
  - At last a name for the no name group, 2003, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - At last a name for the no name group, June 19, 2003
  - The Bakaly prosecution as precedent, July 12, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Banking online in a new millennium, May 1999 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Banking online in a new millennium, May 19, 1999
  - The battle over voter ID, October 1999 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - The battle over voter ID, October 9, 1999
  - Block that smut!, September 18, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Budgets bursting in air, March 27, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Budgets bursting in air, March 27, 1999
  - Business leaders endorse RCC (Reston Community Center) outreach, July-December 1998 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Business leaders endorse RCC (Reston Community Center) outreach, December 14, 1998
  - Business seats on RCC's (Reston Community Center) board?, October 21, 1998, November 25, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Business seats on RCC's board?, November 25, 2002
  - Byrne's bedroom bill, January 27-28, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Campaign flyers, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Camping and saving lives in Africa, September 2003 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Camping and saving lives in Africa, September 23, 2003
  - Citizens win a voice on phone towers, November 1999 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Citizens win a voice on phone towers, November 18, 1999
  - Columns, 1993-2002 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    Multiple articles and research. Articles include, A Wise Man, Right or Wrong and A Historic Vote Against War.
    - A historic vote against war, May 1, 1999
  - Columns, 1999-2005 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    Includes multiple articles and research material. Articles include, Who's My Senator?; Walking in Reston in the New Year; Lower Taxes! Better Teachers!; Cars v. Transit; Trusting God in School; A City Center in Reston for Dulles Corridor; New Sales Tax Revenue: How Will it be Spent?; Will We Tax Ourselves to Fight Traffic Congestion and Air Pollution?; Touring Reston in Cyberspace; Tom Davis as Nimby? Say it ain't so!; Uncapping Reston Assessments; How the Lawyers Stole a Presidential Election; Marriage Discrimination; Reston Governance by Referendum; Court Dismisses RA Governance by Referendum; TRW Comes to Town; Partisanship and Governance; Sex and Virginia Law; Can Taxes be a Blessing for RA?; Promising Performances; Putting Education to the Test; No Shield for Reporters; The Vincent Cannonade; NVCC Comes Big Time to Reston; An Election Scramble; Voting Against Candidates; Republican Woes.
    - An election scramble, February 23, 2005
    - Can taxes be a blessing for RA (Reston Association)?, May 28, 2003
    - Cars v. transit, June 24, 2002
    - A city center in Reston for Dulles corridor, November 6, 2002
    - Lower taxes! Better teachers!, January 3, 2002
    - Marriage discrimination, July 28, 2004
    - NVCC comes big time to Reston, December 29, 2004
    - Partisanship and governance, February 22, 2000
    - Promising performance, December 31, 2003
    - Putting education to the test, November 7, 1998
    - Reston governance by referendum?, March 15, 2001
    - Sex and Virginia law, February 2, 2005
    - Tom Davis as Nimby? Say it ain't so!, April 24, 2005
    - Touring Reston in cyberspace, July 18, 2001
    - Trusting God in school, August 7, 2002
    - Voting against candidates, May 25, 2004
    - Walking in Reston in the New Year, December 28, 2001
    - Will we tax ourselves to fight traffic congestion and air pollution?, April 2, 2002
  - Coming to Lake Anne, December 1998 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Coming to Lake Anne, December 31, 1998
  - Communicating while growing, February 27-29, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Communicating while growing, February 29, 2000
  - Comparing amenities and costs (Columbia vs. Reston), 1997-2000 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Comparing amenities and costs, March 10, 2000
  - Congestion pricing for Dulles tolls, 1998-1999 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Congestion pricing for Dulles tolls, August 13, 1999
  - Court dismisses RA (Reston Association) governance by referendum, June 25, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Court dismisses RA governance by referendum, June 25, 1999
  - Cross country trail (hikers and bikers rejoice), January 2000 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Cross country trail (hikers and bikers), January 25, 2000
  - Culinary virtuosity invades Fairfax County, February-March 2003 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Culinary virtuosity invades Fairfax County, March 24, 2003
  - Deductible gifts to RA (Reston Association) projects?, 1998-2000 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Deductible gifts to RA (Reston Association) projects?, January 31, 2000
  - Defusing the merger; accounting time bomb, June 28, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Edge city review, 1997-1999 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Elected officials push transit triangle; NoVA 2020 transportation plan, August 27, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Elected officials push transit triangle, August 27, 1999
    - Environmentalists oppose laws to ease traffic congestion, February 2001 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Environmentalists oppose laws to ease traffic congestion, February 24, 2001
  - Fast food and seat belts, January-February 2003 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Fast food and seat belts, February 3, 2003
  - The final solution for deer, October 1998 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - The final solution for deer, October 28, 1998
  - Finding the way to Dulles airport, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Finding the way to Dulles airport, August 12, 1998
  - Fresh value space at Lake Anne, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - George W. writes a letter, June 2000 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - George W. writes a letter, June 2, 2000
  - Getting east and west together, August 2, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Gilmore boards the train... (cheers) ...short on cash (groans), September 1999 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Gilmore boards the train... (cheers) ...short on cash (groans), September 3, 1999
  - Give governors a shot at two terms, February 25-26, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Give governors a shot at two terms, February 26, 2003
  - Gore emails swallowed by blackhole, 1999-2000 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Gore emails swallowed by blackhole, June 16, 2000
  - Government by walkout, July 30, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Government by walkout, July 30, 2003
  - Greenway lessons, August 3-4, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Greenway lessons, August 4, 1999
  - Healthy political turmoil, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Heroes will be heroes, June 1998 (Box 22, Folder 78)
  - High occupancy on the toll road, December 16, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - High occupancy on the toll road, December 16, 1998
  - Home sweet classroom; Homeschooling; Tysons, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    Includes color slide of Citroen car.
  - Instant internet access from Reston, January 5-6, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Instant internet access from Reston, January 6, 2000
  - Is fighting blight corporate welfare?, May-July 1998 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Is there a geriatric cure for RA (Reston Association)?, July 1, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Is there a geriatric cure for RA (Reston Association)?, July 1, 1999
  - Janet Howell reaching across the aisle, October 1999 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Janet Howell reaching across the aisle, October 21, 1999
  - Janet Howell vs. Rosie Scenario, August 2001 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Janet Howell vs. Rosie Scenario, August 22, 2001
  - A joint venture with benefits of a town, 1994-1998 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - A joint venture with benefits of a town, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - The Kain mutiny, December 4-5, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - The Kain mutiny, December 5, 1998
  - Lake Anne Coalition, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Lake Anne historic district, 1993-1997 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Lawless enforcement of environmental laws, June 2000 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Lawless enforcement of environmental laws, June 11, 2000
  - The Leadership of Bob Dix, October 1999 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - The Leadership of Bob Dix, October 14, 1999
  - Let their be light at Reston crossroads, March-June 1999 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Let their be light at Reston crossroads, June 14, 1999
  - A literacy manifesto at Sallie Mae, March-April 2000 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - A literacy manifesto at Sallie Mae, April 4, 2000
  - Long live the President, January-February 1999 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Long live the President, February 1, 1999
  - Making school yards trailer parks; funding schools, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Making school yards trailer parks, May 2, 2000
  - Making the most of a New Year, December 1999 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Making the most of a New Year, December 23, 1999
  - Marginalizing arts in the schools, November 29-30, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Marginalizing arts in the schools, November 30, 1999
  - A master executive (Robert O'Neill Jr.) comes and goes, November-December 1999 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - A master executive (Robert O'Neill Jr.) comes and goes, December 2, 1999
  - Metrorail to Tyson's corner...and beyond?, January 22-23, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Metrorail to Tyson's corner...and beyond?, January 23, 1999
  - More people, less power?, April 23-24, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - More people, less power?, April 24, 2001
  - The nexus of nimbies and naysters, June 23, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - The nexus of nimbies and naysters, June 23, 2001
  - Oscar finds great art at what cost?, March 27, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Passing the RCC (Reston Community Center) torch from mother to daughter, September 12, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Passing the RCC (Reston Community Center) torch from mother to daughter, September 12, 1998
  - Performing arts bloom at RCC (Reston Community Center), April 21-24, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Performing arts bloom at RCC (Reston Community Center), April 24, 1999
  - Pocalyko named campaign lauriate, October-November 1999 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Pocalyko named campaign lauriate, November 1, 1999
  - Poison ivy patch poisons Reston county ties, May 2000 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Poison ivy patch poisons Reston county ties, May 16, 2000
  - The politics of taxes and transportation, July 22, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Polling for RCC (Reston Community Center) governors, October 2003, September 2004 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Polling for RCC (Reston Community Center) governors, September 28, 2004
  - Presidential justice and truth, April 23, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Presidential justice and truth, April 23, 2000
  - Primary republicans go democratic, June 20-21, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Primary republicans go democratic, June 21, 1999
  - Prison fellowship: Saving more lives, 1998-1999 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Prison fellowship: Saving more lives, October 5, 1999
  - Putting education to the test, November 3-7, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Putting education to the test, November 7, 1998
  - RA (Reston Association) election, 1999-2000 (Box 24, Folder 11)